♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll reset it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
Come on, come on!
Ugh, I- I’m so darn lame!
Hi, Einstein.
Hey.
You look awfully down today, what’s the problem?
I’ve been spinning my wheels for days now on Aelita’s--
--antivirus and trying to decode Franz Hopper’s diary.
Just a question of time.
You think so?
Even with the latest data we got from Sector Five,
I haven’t moved ahead one micron! What if I’m just…
...just not good enough?
Uh, okay,
I think I know someone who needs to air out his neurons a little.
And here’s how to do it. Tonight,
Odd is screening his short film.
Anyone seen any of it?
He wouldn’t let us?
Do we know who’s in it, at least?
Humbly speaking, I don’t think it’s unfair to say that this--
--first role will reveal to the entire world my true star personality.
Can you sum up the story for us,
in just a few words for the Kadic News?
Oh, well, that is, uh, it’s a love story,
and at the same time, it’s a thriller!
With suspense, and of course,
it’s got a good dose of psychology.
and- and- and it’s very funny,
a real comedy, and, uh, quite satirical.
So you have no idea?
Uh, I gotta go, someone’s calling me!
(GIGGLING)
Welcome to the Kadic Academy cinema club’s short film night!
Charlie Chaplin, Ziga Cerkov--
How’s it going, Odd? No butterflies yet?
No, I’m- I’m- I’m cool.
You’d never guess.
...to full-length features, which is also why I’ll be…
Relax, I’m sure you’re gonna be great.
Thanks, that’s sweet. Uh, but,
move your hand or lose it at the elbow.
...the short film is, was, and always will be an important art form,
which can say as much as a full-length feature.
Our first film is by Odd Della-Robbia, and is entitled, rather poetically,
“Natural Grandeur”. No one has seen it yet, but it isn’t hard to imagine
a project, perhaps, of the fragility of our ecosystem, which- er--
Hmph.
Hmhm.
Hmm.
Help! Help! She’s awake, oh no!
What’s all this racket about, huh?
(LAUGHTER)
Ahahaha- oh?
We have to get out of here! She- she-
she’s coming! I tell you, she’s as big as her ego!
That’s impossible!
You know how big that would make her.
Hmm.
I think you’ve lost your senses.
Alright, let’s go to the infirmary.
(LAUGHTER)
No!
Huh?
It’s too late! She’s found us!
Oh rats, I just broke a nail!
(LAUGHTER)
I didn’t know you could be so funny.
Aaah!
Odd! You are nothing but a-
you’re nothing but a…
(GIBBERISH)
Is something wrong, sweetheart?
I’ll take care of this, Mr. Delmas.
I think you’ve lost your senses.
Alright, let’s go to the infirmary.
(LAUGHTER)
Alright, children,
I want each of you to go quietly back to your rooms.
Jim, take care of the students.
I’ll take Sissi to the infirmary.
You think it’s…
...XANA?
Nope. No activated towers.
XANA’s got nothing to do with it.
The nurse said that Sissi received an electric charge.
She’s in shock, but fine, there’s nothing to worry about.
Oh poor Sissi. I have to admit that her acting was really electrifying .
Right. False alarm. We can all sleep easy now.
Yeah, that works out just fine,
because tomorrow is Sunday, and on Sunday--
--we sleep in!
Huh?
(GIBBERISH)
Sissi!
Sissi, what has gotten into you, huh?
What’s all this racket about?
Sissi? You should be in the infirmary,
your father’s going to have my head again.
(PHONE RINGING)
Jeremie, it’s Sunday…
Okay, we’re coming.
A message in code? Written by Sissi?
Uh-huh. I ran the Supercomputer all night to translate it.
And look at what it turned up!
(GIBBERISH)
...I can help you. I want to enter into contact with you.
“I can help you”?
It has to be a trap by XANA.
He must’ve managed somehow to--
--possess Sissi without activating a tower.
I don’t think so. Otherwise,
Sissi would have gone after me.
She would’ve tried to get me out to Lyoko,
so that the Scyphozoa could steal my memory.
Aelita’s right. If you ask me, someone, or something,
wants to contact us through Sissi, but it’s not XANA.
Well then, who is it?
No idea. To find that out,
we’ll have to talk to Sissi again.
Okay, I’ll bring her over. Anyone care to join me?
I will. I’m your man, Yumi.
I mean-- you know what I mean.
I’d better go take a look around Lyoko.
I still wanna make sure XANA isn’t setting some sort of trap.
I’ll go with you.
With the Scyphozoa and everything? It’s too risky.
Jeremie, stop worrying about me.
Transfer Ulrich,
Transfer Aelita,
Scanner Ulrich,
Scanner Aelita,
Virtualization!
Great timing. Nice work, Jeremie.
Thanks.
Okay, make it fast, it’s just a reconnaissance mission.
We know. Relax, we won’t go crazy.
Yeah!
Jeremie, bad news. Sissi’s going to the hospital.
Oh no, we have to bring her back here!
No sweat, I’ve got an idea.
Are you thinking what I think you’re thinking?
Yeah. good thinking.
Ulrich, Aelita, everything okay with you guys?
To tell you the truth, I have no idea.
Has the Superscan picked up an activated tower?
No, still nothing, why?
Well… hang on, I’ll send you a visual.
What the heck is this white tower supposed to mean?
I was about to ask you the same thing.
Do you think this tower has something to do with Sissi?
Or with the being who's trying to contact us?
I don’t know.
Come on, I’d like to see this close up.
Ulrich, behind you!
Faster!
I’ve got it floored!
Turn left!
Woah, are you sure? There’s nothing to the left!
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
Well done Aelita,
but it’s really weird that they didn’t come back to attack you.
Something’s not right.
Jeremie, it wasn’t us they were after.
They’re trying to destroy the white tower!
Hold them off.
Feel like a little game of bowling?
Of what?
Forget about it, it’s a bad joke.
Sometimes, I really crack myself up.
Well, what’s wrong with her?
I haven’t the slightest idea.
We’ll keep her here under observation
for a few hours, and then we’ll see.
Oh, very well.
Let me know at the first sign of a change in her condition.
Of course.
...such a sweet patient, he was really lucky…
So what did the girl at the reception say?
Room 237.
Huh?
(PHONE RINGING)
Jeremie?
I’ve just located an activated tower.
XANA is on the offensive!
(SCREAMING)
Jeremie, I’ll call you back.
Stop!
Poor thing. She had hypertension.
Not anymore. Quick!
It’s okay, Jeremie, we’ve got Sissi.
Great! Bring her over to the factory and hurry up!
It won’t be that easy.
There’s a doctor possessed by XANA who doesn’t seem to like the idea.
Ouch.
Ulrich, I’ve got some bad news.
Hang on.
So, Jeremie, what were you saying?
Activated tower in the ice sector.
What should I do with Aelita?
Protect this tower or deactivate the other one?
Ulrich!
Huh?
Jeremie, what do we do?
Uh, protect the white tower!
You know, I could go deactivate that tower.
All alone? No way. It’s too dangerous.
I’ll get rid of this one,
and after that, we’ll go together.
Look!
Aelita, stay next to me.
No, Aelita, don’t do it!
Aelita!
Let’s get out of here!
Here comes Doctor Doom!
Look out!
I hope she was wearing a seatbelt.
Huh?
Cool.
Phew.
Ulrich?
Relax, Jeremie, I’m on it.
Now that has got to hurt.
Woah.
Quick!
Ah, finally.
Yumi, what are you doing?
I’m buying time.
Sissi, I believe that-- h-hey!
Sissi, now what’s the matter with you?
Wait. Let her go.
Aelita, look out!
Get to Lyoko! Quick!
Jeremie, I can’t hold out much longe- aaah!
Sissi!
Virtualization!
Odd!
Run, Aelita! Run!
Odd, watch it, you’ve just lost 80 life points.
One more hit and it’s game over!
Relax, it’s all part of the plan.
Something wrong with the elevator?
I’ll explain later. Hurry on up to help Yumi.
Get on.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
Yumi!
(HUMMING CONTINUES)
Tower deactivated.
Wow! Great job, Aelita!
Huh? Everything okay, Sissi?
How do you expect everything to be okay,
when I’m surrounded by big, fat losers?
Did I miss something?
(LAUGHTER)
Come on, tell me.
Yes. Odd just offered Sissi a role in his next film.
It’s the story of this girl, driven by this mysterious being,
who tried to make contact with humans.
All of which takes place in a virtual universe full of danger!
What did she say?
That no one would ever believe such a ridiculous story.
(LAUGHING)
You don’t say?
What about you, how’s it going?
Finished! The computer deciphered all of--
--the lines of code that Sissi spoke while she was spellbound.
So, what’s it say? Let’s hear it!
Tons of interesting stuff, and a whole lot of elements--
--that are going to help me find the antivirus for Aelita.
And... do you know who this mysterious entity--
--who wants to get into contact with us is?
Well… Take a look.
I’m warning you, this is completely crazy.
(GIBBERISH)
...I can help you.
I want to enter into contact with you now…
Wow, I can’t believe it!
I am Franz Hopper.
I am Franz Hopper?
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS